<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>print design on Marie Yatsyk</title>
    <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/tags/print-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in print design on Marie Yatsyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:26:52 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marieyatsyk.com/tags/print-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shout Your Worth</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/shout-your-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:26:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/shout-your-worth/</guid>
      <description>Shout Your Worth is a game-like toolkit to help people communicate their value. It teaches the value statement format for talking about one&#39;s accomplishments, which is a proven technique taught in AAUW salary negotiation workshops. Shout Your Worth was created for my Interaction Design capstone project at Northeastern University.
ShoutYourWorth.com Players craft value statements using Accomplishment, Skill, and Result cards, then share real-world experiences that illustrate those value statements. Collaborative gameplay creates a supportive, encouraging environment for players to practice this self-advocacy skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Cover Series</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/book-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 20:32:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/book-series/</guid>
      <description>These book covers are for a hypothetical series about three influential architects. I designed them for the Typography II course at Northeastern University.
I wanted to showcase the unique aspects of each architect&#39;s works, and for this I drew inspiration from the architects&#39; drafting sketches, which give an fascinating glimpse into their thought process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeastern University Marketing Association</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/numa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:53:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/numa/</guid>
      <description>Promotional Flyers From January-December 2016, I wrote and designed the flyers for the Northeastern University Marketing Association&#39;s (NUMA) weekly meetings. I also designed matching social media graphics for Facebook events, Instagram posts, and website banners.
Logo Design In fall 2016, I re-designed the logo for the Northeastern University Marketing Association to help with their re-branding on campus. The new logo projects a polished and bold image, but also retains the approachability of the old logo through the rounded letterforms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
