<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Print Design on Marie Yatsyk</title>
    <link>http://marieyatsyk.com/tags/print-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Print Design on Marie Yatsyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:26:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://marieyatsyk.com/tags/print-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shout Your Worth</title>
      <link>http://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/shout-your-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:26:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/shout-your-worth/</guid>
      <description>Shout Your Worth is a game-like toolkit to help you communicate your value. It teaches the value statement format for talking about their accomplishments — which is a proven technique taught in AAUW salary negotiation workshops.  Shout Your Worth was created for the Interaction Design Senior Capstone team project at Northeastern University.
 ShoutYourWorth.com       Players craft value statements using Accomplishment, Skill, and Result cards, then share real-world experiences that illustrate those value statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Cover Series</title>
      <link>http://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/book-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 20:32:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/book-series/</guid>
      <description>For a Typography II assignment, I designed these book covers for a hypothetical series for the Canadian Center of Architecture about three influential architects: Louis Sullivan, Richard Neutra, and Frank Gehry.
 I wanted to showcase the unique aspects of each architect&#39;s works, and for this I drew inspiration from the architects&#39; drafting sketches, which give an fascinating glimpse into their thought process.
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeastern University Marketing Association</title>
      <link>http://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/numa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:53:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/numa/</guid>
      <description>Promotional Flyers From January-December 2016, I wrote and designed the flyers for the club&#39;s weekly meetings, as well as the corresponding social media graphics (Facebook event header images, square graphics for Instagram posts, and banners for NUMA&#39;s website home page).
          Logo Design  I designed the logo for the Northeastern University Marketing Association to help with their re-branding on campus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>