<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Marie Yatsyk</title>
    <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Marie Yatsyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 22:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Index Card Collages</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/index-card-collage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/index-card-collage/</guid>
      <description>#004 Hope in a Vial2022-01-29
#003 Quarantine Year 32022-01-09
#002 Luck and prosperity in NYC2021-07-17
#001 Peace from chaos2021-07-17</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starlings</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/starlings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 23:05:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/starlings/</guid>
      <description>This abstract sculpture was inspired by the movement of starling murmurations. I created it as part of the 3D Fundamentals course at Northeastern University. Process For inspiration, I watched the video below on repeat and sketched the abstract forms of the flying birds. I then carved my favorite sketch into floral foam, after which I used a 3D scanner to digitize the sculpture, and sliced it into 52 pieces for the laser cutter using SketchUp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shout Your Worth</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/shout-your-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:26:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/shout-your-worth/</guid>
      <description>Shout Your Worth is a game-like toolkit to help people communicate their value. It teaches the value statement format for talking about one&#39;s accomplishments, which is a proven technique taught in AAUW salary negotiation workshops. Shout Your Worth was created for my Interaction Design capstone project at Northeastern University.
ShoutYourWorth.com Players craft value statements using Accomplishment, Skill, and Result cards, then share real-world experiences that illustrate those value statements. Collaborative gameplay creates a supportive, encouraging environment for players to practice this self-advocacy skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When One Door Closes, Another Opens</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/when-one-door-closes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:21:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/when-one-door-closes/</guid>
      <description>I created an interactive sculpture inspired by this quote: When one door closes, another opens; but we often look so long and so regretfully upon the closed door that we do not see the one which has opened for us. — Alexander Graham Bell This quote felt very relevant to my senior semester of college, and I wanted to create a playful piece that invited audiences to interact and engage with it while being self-reflective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Good Spirits</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/in-good-spirits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:18:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/in-good-spirits/</guid>
      <description>For the 2019 Global Game Jam, I worked on a team with six other students to build a video game from scratch in 48 hours. The year&#39;s theme was &#34;Home&#34;, and we were inspired by the idea of apartment buildings, where so many strangers live in close proximity but many of whom never even meet. We created In Good Spirits, a 2D puzzle game where you play as a ghost haunting an apartment building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>f(x) foods</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/fx-foods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:03:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/fx-foods/</guid>
      <description>In Fall 2018, I worked as a Studio Developer for Scout. In four months, our five-person student team (three designers, two developers) created a new brand identity and assets, packaging, a brand book, and a fully-functional marketing and e-commerce website for our client – a young granola bar company started by a Northeastern alumna. For the first half of the semester I focused on user experience design, helping create lo-fi packaging and website wireframes in addition to conducting user research and iterating on logo designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippines Country Data</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/country-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 23:13:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/country-data/</guid>
      <description>I created this poster for the Information Design course at Northeastern University. We were asked to present 30 pieces of information about a country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Jam</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:30:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/jam/</guid>
      <description>I created this poster for the Information Design class at Northeastern University.
We were asked to show a process with at least 10 steps, using as few words as possible. I used watercolors to illustrate each step of the process.
Colophon: Playfair Display</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Trips Visualization</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/3-trips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 20:31:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/3-trips/</guid>
      <description> This piece presents information about three trips: from my apartment to a classroom, from my apartment to my parents&#39; home in New York, and from New York to Moscow.
I created this 7-panel accordion for the Information Design class at Northeastern University. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Cat Comic</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/night-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 22:19:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/night-cat/</guid>
      <description>I created this comic as a submission for the One Page Stinkers comics zine. It tells the story of a cat&#39;s dream about the big night cat in the sky. This comic was published in Issue #9.
Media: ink and watercolor on cream sketchbook paper</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TripKick Travel Sidekick App Design</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/tripkick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 01:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/tripkick/</guid>
      <description>TripKick is a travel sidekick app that helps streamline the trip-planning process from research to on-the-go.
Users start by collecting information about hotels, flights trip destinations in a browser extension / web application. From there, they can create a trip itinerary, and install the TripKick mobile app.
In the time leading up to the trip, TripKick notifies users of dropped prices and discounts for their travel plans.
During the trip, the app helps users navigate to their destinations, review attractions on TripAdvisor, and find alternate activities in case events get rained out or change hours unexpectedly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change Poster</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:40:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/climate-change/</guid>
      <description>This dramatic poster uses data from climate.nasa.gov to showcase evidence of climate change, with a focus on melting polar ice caps.
When I learned about global warming as a kid, I remember feeling a powerful urgency to try and change things. I tried to create an attention-grabbing poster that would both inform viewers and get them equally concerned about this issue.
I created this poster for the Typography II course at Northeastern University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Cover Series</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/book-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 20:32:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/book-series/</guid>
      <description>These book covers are for a hypothetical series about three influential architects. I designed them for the Typography II course at Northeastern University.
I wanted to showcase the unique aspects of each architect&#39;s works, and for this I drew inspiration from the architects&#39; drafting sketches, which give an fascinating glimpse into their thought process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spooky FM Video Game</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/spookyfm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 00:56:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/spookyfm/</guid>
      <description>Title screen art by R. Giraud During the 2017 Global Game Jam, I worked on a team with six other students to build a video game from scratch in 48 hours. We created Spooky FM, a 2D side-scrolling survival game where you play as a radio DJ who tries to appease an influx of monsters by playing their favorite music. Battle your station’s awful WiFI connection and your own caffeine dependency while making sure to fulfill audience requests to keep the ratings up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Marketing Headline Generator</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/marketing-headline-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 01:17:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/marketing-headline-generator/</guid>
      <description> Just for fun, I created this generator that combines randomly-chosen buzzwords and business terms to create surprisingly plausible Business-to-Business content marketing headlines. Click to generate a new listicle headline.
&gt;&gt; View on GitHub </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MindSet Web App Design</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 00:48:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/mindset/</guid>
      <description>MindSet is a mood and habit tracking web app that helps users manage their stress by allowing them to track their weekly schedule (calendar data), to-do lists, habits, and other factors that affect their mood (such as exercise, amount of sleep, caffeine intake, etc.).
Based on that data, the app makes suggestions for what the user should do each week to help improve their mood, such as: take a 20 minute nap on certain days, limit caffeine intake, sit in the sun, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typeface Posters</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/type-posters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 00:34:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/type-posters/</guid>
      <description>A promotional poster for the Gotham typeface, intended to be as clean, bold, and eye-catching as the type.
This poster showcases letter-forms around Boston and Cambridge using a collage of photos I took myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letterforms</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/letterforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:42:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/letterforms/</guid>
      <description>I created these logo-like letterforms for the Typography I course at Northeastern university. I like to imagine them as decorations on a fancy purse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather App</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/weather-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 01:22:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/weather-app/</guid>
      <description> This simple web app connects to the OpenWeatherMap and Flickr APIs to show weather in a city and a lovely random image of said city.
&gt;&gt; View on GitHub This was my first-ever web app, and was originally built at the HubSpot Women&#39;s WebApp Workshop, Fall 2016. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeastern University T-Shirt Design</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/neu-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:51:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/neu-shirt/</guid>
      <description> Created for a contest organized by the Saint Stephen Street and Huntington (S.S. Huntington) dorms at Northeastern University.
Process </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Coding Experiments</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/creative-coding-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 01:08:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/creative-coding-experiments/</guid>
      <description>Just a silly self-portrait created using canvas shapes. Try clicking my face!
A zen, randomly-generated pattern inspired by a mermaid&#39;s scales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxious Tale</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/anxious-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 20:32:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/anxious-tale/</guid>
      <description> This interactive narrative was created in response to the prompt &#34;elicit an emotion.&#34; I chose to explore the sensation of social anxiety. I also wanted to challenge myself to see if I could create a sense of unease and discomfort through simple ASCII art-like illustrations. &gt;&gt; Experience the story </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sound Visualizer</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/sound-visualizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 01:19:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/sound-visualizer/</guid>
      <description>This was one of my first ever coding projects, created for the Programming Basics course at Northeastern University. I wanted to create an interactive sound visualizer that responds to audio and user input.
&gt;&gt; View on GitHub The mouse-following particle effects use a modified version of the particle effects are easy script by Hunter Loftis, and the particle size is tied to the volume of the sound captured from the browser microphone (using the p5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vector Art Experiments</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/vector-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 01:05:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/vector-art/</guid>
      <description>A portrait of one of my favorite musicians: Dessa.
Each flower was meticulously drawn using tiny straight lines, as a challenge in using the Adobe Illustrator pen tool without drawing curves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeastern University Marketing Association</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/numa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:53:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/numa/</guid>
      <description>Promotional Flyers From January-December 2016, I wrote and designed the flyers for the Northeastern University Marketing Association&#39;s (NUMA) weekly meetings. I also designed matching social media graphics for Facebook events, Instagram posts, and website banners.
Logo Design In fall 2016, I re-designed the logo for the Northeastern University Marketing Association to help with their re-branding on campus. The new logo projects a polished and bold image, but also retains the approachability of the old logo through the rounded letterforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There the form stood, motionless as the hill beneath.</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/linocut-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 00:46:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/linocut-hill/</guid>
      <description>This print was inspired by a passage in Thomas Hardy’s Return of the Native. It describes the lone figure of Eustacia Vye standing silhouetted on a barrow, while in the distance the other villages light bonfires, one by one, all across the heath. This project was my first foray into linoleum printmaking, and it enabled me to play around with different color combinations as a way of conveying different atmospheres.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
