<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>code on Marie Yatsyk</title>
    <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/tags/code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in code on Marie Yatsyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:03:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marieyatsyk.com/tags/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>f(x) foods</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/fx-foods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:03:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/fx-foods/</guid>
      <description>In Fall 2018, I worked as a Studio Developer for Scout. In four months, our five-person student team (three designers, two developers) created a new brand identity and assets, packaging, a brand book, and a fully-functional marketing and e-commerce website for our client – a young granola bar company started by a Northeastern alumna.  For the first half of the semester I focused on user experience design, helping create lo-fi packaging and website wireframes in addition to conducting user research and iterating on logo designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Marketing Headline Generator</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/marketing-headline-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 01:17:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/marketing-headline-generator/</guid>
      <description>Just for fun, I created this generator that combines randomly-chosen buzzwords and business terms to create surprisingly plausible B2B content marketing headlines.
 View on GitHub        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather App</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/weather-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 01:22:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/weather-app/</guid>
      <description> This simple web app connects to the OpenWeatherMap and Flickr APIs to show weather in a city and a lovely random image of said city.
 View on GitHub  This was my first-ever web app, and was originally built at the HubSpot Women&#39;s WebApp Workshop, Fall 2016.       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Coding Experiments</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/creative-coding-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 01:08:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/creative-coding-experiments/</guid>
      <description> Just a silly self-portrait created using canvas shapes. Try clicking my face!
   A zen, randomly-generated pattern inspired by a mermaid&#39;s scales.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxious Tale</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/anxious-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 20:32:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/anxious-tale/</guid>
      <description> This interactive narrative was created in response to the prompt &#34;elicit an emotion.&#34; I chose to explore the sensation of social anxiety. I also wanted to challenge myself to see if I could create a sense of unease and discomfort through very simple ASCII art-like illustrations.   Experience the story   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sound Visualizer</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/sound-visualizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 01:19:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/sound-visualizer/</guid>
      <description>This was one of my first ever coding projects, created for the Programming Basics course at Northeastern University. I wanted to create an interactive sound visualizer that responds to audio and user input.
 View on GitHub  The mouse-following particle effects use a modified version of the particle effects are easy script by Hunter Loftis, and the particle size is tied to the volume of the sound captured from the browser microphone (using the p5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>