<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>information design on Marie Yatsyk</title>
    <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/tags/information-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in information design on Marie Yatsyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 23:13:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marieyatsyk.com/tags/information-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippines Country Data</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/country-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 23:13:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/country-data/</guid>
      <description>  I created this poster for the Information Design course at Northeastern University. We were asked to present 30 pieces of information about a country.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Jam</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:30:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/jam/</guid>
      <description>I created this poster for the Information Design class at Northeastern University.
We were asked to show a process with at least 10 steps, using as few words as possible. I used watercolors to illustrate each step of the process.
Colophon: Playfair Display</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Trips Visualization</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/3-trips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 20:31:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/3-trips/</guid>
      <description> This piece presents information about three trips: from my apartment to a classroom, from my apartment to my parents&#39; home in New York, and from New York to Moscow.
 I created this 7-panel accordion for the Information Design class at Northeastern University. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change Poster</title>
      <link>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:40:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marieyatsyk.com/portfolio/climate-change/</guid>
      <description>This dramatic poster uses data from climate.nasa.gov to showcase evidence of climate change, with a focus on melting polar ice caps.
When I learned about global warming as a kid, I remember feeling a powerful urgency to try and change things. I tried to create an attention-grabbing poster that would both inform viewers and get them equally concerned about this issue.
I created this poster for the Typography II course at Northeastern University.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>